

Contacts

- **Phone** +7 (963)-747-37-32
- Telegram
 https://t.me/stpkk
- Email stipyk1309@gmail.com
- GitHub
 https://github.com/stpkkk
- in LinkedIn

 www.linkedin.com/in/igorstepanov1
- Address
 Russia, Petrozavodsk

My portfolio website: https://next-js-stpkkkportfolio.vercel.app/

Skills

- Next.js
- React
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Redux
- Rest API
- Styled Components
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind
- Git
- Figma
- Responsive and crossbrowser layout
- English C1 Advanced

IGOR STEPANOV

FRONTEND-DEVELOPER

About Me

A frontend-developer with experience in creating web applications using React. Good knowledge in JavaScript, TypeScript and related libraries.

Paying close attention to details, it's important for me that the code is clean, well-organized, and error-free.

Great team member, worked both in large team and as a solid developer.

Have an active life position - there are a lot of sports in my life, i love cycling and snowboarding.

Ready for full time or part time work.

Open to your suggestions and new oppotunities.

Experience

Technomedia (Petrozavodsk) June 2022 - February 2024

React-developer

- Worked in development of web-application "Business insurance calculator" using React, Typescript and Styled Components
- Worked in updating layouts, adding content and SEO optimization to company's main website sysdyn.ru
- Worked in development of functional components for companies projects
- Admin side development

Rukki Pro (Moscow) August 2021 - May 2022

React-developer

Implementation of the interface on the stack Next.js/React/Typescript/Styled Components Joined the project at the final stage and successfully joined to team.

I successfully eliminated all interface bugs, optimized the application, at the moment I'm finishing the implementation of all business requirements and, together with the team, I am preparing the project for production.

Freelance February 2021 - Jule 2021

Frontend-developer

- Creating website layouts based in template, using HTML5 and CSS3
- Engaged in SEO optimization and website promotion
- · Design creation for websites in Figma
- Development of Adaptive and Crossbrowser layouts

Education

2022 Jonas Schmedtmann,

Udemy
 The Ultimate React Course 2023 React, Redux & More
 Jonas Schmedtmann, The complete JavaScript Course:

Udemy From Zero to Expert

2011-2014 Management and Cadastre, Cadastral Engineer

Petrozavodsk State University